The way you never cease to seize your dreams
Inspires me to be-
Inspires me to be like you
And your determination
And your determination gets to me
Yeah, that's the part that makes me
Want to be with you
With the universe above
You persist, reaching
Into the endless
Into the endless string of time
While you chase the impossible
I'll be there for you 'cause
I know till then you
I know till then you'll still be mine
With the universe above
You persist, reaching
Into the endless
Into the endless string of time
While you chase the impossible
I'll be there for you
I'll be there for YOU 'CAUSE
I
I KNOW
I know TILL
I know till THEN
I know till then YOU'LL
I know till then you'll BE
I know till then you'll be MINE
In the endless string of time
In the endless string of time!
With the universe above
With the universe ABOVE!!